https://www.seawaychina.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Seaway China Company has partnered with Lion and Unicorn Auctioneers on a new adventure! Although these items are not available, we hold monthly auctions with 100s of Royal Doulton, Lladro and other Collectibles. Please be sure to visit lionandunicorn.com for our upcoming auction.
Explore Our Auctions
About Us
About the Owners
Contact Us
Shipping & Returns
Payment Options
Visit Our Gallery
Museums & Exhibitions
Privacy Policy
Legal Notices
Conditions of Use
Privacy Policy
We at Seaway China place great value on your privacy and have created a privacy policy to demonstrate this firm commitment. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website, www.seawaychina.com:
We do not share any personal information gathered online with outside companies.
Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We use this information solely within the company to improve our site and services.
Our site uses “cookies” technology as a means of keeping track of your shopping cart. A “cookie” is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
This site contains links to other sites. Seaway China is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor’s contact information (like their name and email address) and financial information (like their credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is only used to bill the user for products and services.
SECURITY
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All order transactions are conducted via a secure server.
CHOICE/OPT-OUT
Our site provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.
Seaway China offers you the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can email us
You can send mail to the following postal address:
485 South Federal Highway, Dania Beach, FL 33004
You can call the following telephone number: 800.968.2424
CORRECT/UPDATE
Seaway China offers you the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
You can email us
You can send mail to the following postal address:
485 South Federal Highway, Dania Beach, FL 33004
You can call the following telephone number: 800.968.2424
CONTACT WEB SITE
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Seaway China in any of the following ways:
You can email us
You can send mail to the following postal address:
485 South Federal Highway, Dania Beach, FL 33004
You can call the following telephone number: 800.968.2424
Search for:
